(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-01T16:17:38.321319",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
青い水平線を いま駆け抜けてく
I’m running past the blue horizon now
ときめかされた 時の流れ感じて
Keenly feeling the flow of time on me
ときめきへと 動き出す世界は
Ah, the world gets going towards something thrilling
忘れかけてた 遠い夢の訪れ
The coming of a distant dream I’d forgotten
Ride On Time さまよう想いなら
Ride On Time, take my wandering thoughts
やさしく受け取めて そっと包んで
And wrap them gently around yourself, oh
Ride On Time 心に火をつけて
Ride On Time, light my heart on fire
あふれる喜びへ 広がれ Ride On Time
Flood me with joy, Ride On Time
僕の輝く未来
C’mon, bright future of mine,
さあ回り始めて
start turning
虚ろな日々も 全て愛に溶け込む
All these hollow days melt away into love
何という朝 今すぐ君のもと
Ah, what a morning! I’ll go deliver
届けに行こう 燃える心迷わず
my fired up heart to you with no hesitation
Ride On Time 時よ走り出せ
Ride On Time, time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining! So bright you make me dizzy
Ride On Time 心に火をつけて
Ride On Time, I’ll light my heart on fire
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride On Time
And send it to your soaring soul, Ride On Time
届けに行こう 燃える心今こそ
I’m gonna go deliver my fired up heart right now
Ride On Time 時よ走り出せ
Ride On Time, time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining! So bright that it makes me dizzy
Ride On Time 心に火をつけて
Ride On Time, I’ll light my heart on fire
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride On Time
And send it to your soaring soul, Ride On Time, oh
Ride On Time さまよう想いなら
Ride On Time, take my wandering thoughts as they are
Ride On Time 時よ走り出せ
Ride On Time, time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining! So bright you make me dizzy
Ride On Time 心に火をつけて
Ride On Time, I’ll light my heart on fire
青い水平線を いま駆け抜けてく
I’m running past the blue horizon now,
ときめき誘われた 時の流れ感じて
keenly feeling the flow of time on me.
AH ときめきへと 動き出す世界は
Ah, the world gets going towards something thrilling,
忘れかけてた 遠い夢の訪れ
the coming of a distant dream I’d forgotten.
RIDE ON TIME さまよう想いなら
Ride on time, take my wandering thoughts as they are,
やさしく受け止めて そっと包んで
and wrap them gently around yourself.
RIDE ON TIME 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light my heart on fire,
あふれる喜びに ひろがれ RIDE ON TIME
flood me with joy, ride on time.
RIDE ON TIME さまよう想いなら
Ride on time, take my wandering thoughts as they are,
やさしく受け止めて そっと包んで
and wrap them gently around yourself.
RIDE ON TIME 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light my heart on fire,
あふれる喜びに ひろがれ RIDE ON TIME
flood me with joy, ride on time.
僕の輝く未来 さぁ回りはじめ
C’mon, bright future of mine, start turning,
虚ろな日々も 全て愛に溶け込む
all these hollow days melt away into love.
何という朝 今すぐ君のもと
Ah, what a morning! I’m going to deliver
届けに行こう 燃える心迷わず
to you right now with zero hesitation.
RIDE ON TIME 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining so bright you make me dizzy,
RIDE ON TIME 心に火を点けて
ride on time, I’ll light my heart on fire
飛び立つ魂に 送るよ RIDE ON TIME
and send it to your soaring soul, ride on time.
RIDE ON TIME さまよう想いなら
Ride on time, take my wandering thoughts as they are,
やさしく受け止めて そっと包んで
and wrap them gently around yourself.
RIDE ON TIME 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light my heart on fire...
ἐκ λόγου ἄλλος εκβαίνει λόγοs
One word brings forth another.
水面に映る自分が言った
My reflection in the water says to me,
「ああ、私は悪いサメです」
"Oh my god, you're such a bad shark."
ずっと恐れていた (ooh)
I was always terrified (ooh)
赤く光るその目
of those glowing red eyes.
海の底
Sinking into the void
暗闇に消えていく
at the bottom of the sea.
どうして (your tired eyes)
Why (your tired eyes)
泣くのよ (begin to fall)
do you cry? (begin to fall)
欲しいものなら全部手に入れた
I gave you everything you craved.
教えて (your darkest thoughts)
Tell me if (your darkest thoughts)
私は (unleash them all)
I can ever be (unleash them all)
望んでいた私になれたかな
the me you wanted me to be.
私はあなたとは違うの
I'm not like you.
やめてよ 決めつけはもう大嫌い
Stop it, I hate the way you judge me.
理想の姿でなくていいの
I don't need to conform to any ideals,
私らしくあれば
I just want to be myself.
ただ分かって欲しいだけよ
Just want to be understood.
過去はいらない そんなことはない
The past isn't important? That's not true.
未来は見えない方がマシじゃない
A life that's unpredictable is brighter.
ここから (no matter where)
From here on out (no matter where)
静かに (watch over me)
just watch quietly (watch over me)
私を見守っていてね
how I live my life.
さようなら (our story ends)
Farewell (our story ends)
ありがとう (begin again)
Thank you (begin again)
隠していた私はもういない
I won't hide my heart's desires anymore.
さようなら (once hand-in-hand)
Farewell (once hand-in-hand)
ありがとう (until the end)
Thank you (until the end)
全て受け入れて生きていくから
I'll accept my everything and live.
Tok-tok-tok Tokyo Wabi-Sabi Lullaby
眠れない夜には Hold me tight
in the sleepless night, hold me tight.
Oh na-na-na-na-na-na-na
ねぇ今年の夏 また会えるかな
hey, will we meet again this summer?
海の匂い 砂の浜 スイカ割り
Scent of the sea, sandy beach, watermelon smashing,
懐かしい故郷の childhood memories
childhood memories of my nostalgic hometown.
夕日暮黄昏 二人だけ
Twilight in the calm, just the two of us,
濡れ髪をかき上げて笑った
brushed back wet hair and laughed.
Tok-tok-tok Tokyo Wabi-Sabi Lullaby
眠れない夜には Hold me tight
in the sleepless night, hold me tight.
Oh na-na-na-na-na-na-na
ねぇ元気してる？ 話したいよ
hey, are you doing well? I want to talk.
「寂しい」を堪えて「またね」と笑っていた
Holding back the "lonely", you laughed and said "see you again".
ああとても綺麗だ 一人で見上げた夜空に花火
Ah, it's so beautiful, fireworks in the night sky I looked up at alone.
stray my heart
何もかも蜃気楼を
it's all a mirage.
夏の女神の 気まぐれね
The whims of the goddess of summer.
いつかまただなんて I never say
See you someday, I never say...
stay my heart
波打ち際 ほどけた 髪 帽子の先
Flowing locks on the shore, beyond the lip of the hat
見覚えある 青いワーゲン stop the flashback
Is a familiar blue wagen stop the flashback
南風の いたずらな魔法ね
The southern winds, a playful magic
遠い夏のあの眩暈に戻さないで again
Don't send me back to the dizzy days of that summer again
唇にぬくもり残して
A lingering warmth on the lips
肩すくめて ボンネットから腰上げて
Shrugging my shoulders, lifting up from the bonnet
語りすぎよ 飽きてきたわ stay the flashlight
Talking too much, getting tired of it, stay the flashlight
Myth or treat
Your oshi's waiting in the closet tonight
No way to stop, she's dead set on giving you a fright
Trick or treat, but now we're all outta candy
Feelin' just a little sick? This chainsaw oughtta come in handy
Chat is blushing, look at those red cheeks
How cute
I'll fix that up, drain all your blood, that's what you seek
Myth or treat!
Myth or treat! Oh, what a cursified stream
There's no bones about it, you'll scream
Only show ya on Halloween, our spooky, terrifying, scarier sides
Oh, what a gachikoi night
Mythic witches with endless spite
Can't escape our idol-esque might
No candy in sight so your souls will suffice
パレード パレード パレード 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's time to take the stage
悔しさもいとおしさも連れて置いて
With all our regrets and sweetness brought along
風よ 夢跳ねろ 飛び越えてるさ
Wind, leap in dreams, jumping right over
ささやかな願いはより大きく
Our modest wishes grow ever larger
終わりなき誓い 君と飛び込んでいく
An endless vow, jumping in together with you
素敵なスタートさ ここから ここから ここから
A wonderful start, right from here, right from here
パレード パレード パレード 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's time to take the stage
悔しさもいとおしさも連れて置いて
With all our regrets and sweetness brought along
Face to face with time again
We walk once more to the end
Burn it down, burn it down
Waves can't put out my flame
Death will never write my name
Burn it down, burn it down
They say the memory of me is fading
I've heard it all before
Don't tell me everyone around is waiting
And they all say
Tear it down, burn it down
And they'll all pay
When I tear it down, burn it down
When the world falls through and all is ash again
While you all pretend if this is the end I'll do it again
Voices rise in my head, the hands that pull at my thread
Let them drown, burn it down
Wait for wash in the tide, in the abyss is where I will hide
will hide
Let them drown
Burn it down
They say the memory of me is fading
I've heard it all before
Don't tell me everyone around is waiting
And they all say Tear it down
Burn it down
And they'll all pay When I tear it down
When the world falls through
And all is ash again
While you all pretend If this is the end
I'll do it again
We swim against the current's aim
In dark we change as smoke returns to rain
Navigating sunken depths and all of its debris
And no more hands upon my words They only speak for me
For all the ones who try to silence thunder
I'm the wave that pulls you down and under
Everyday I'll stand with me And I'll fight the drought of shallow sea
As ships sail winds of jealousy I'll listen carefully
As they all say
Tear it down Burn it down
And they'll all pay
When I tear it down Burn it down
When the world falls through
And all is ash again
While you all pretend If this is the end I'll do it again
I'll do it again
Hi, hello. Hello, hello. Thank you. Hello.
Hi, um, from the very bottom of my shark heart, thank you.
Um, if I could borrow your ear for just a, just a bit more time,
I want to thank you, um, again.
Thank you for letting me be your shark idol for the last
half a decade. Five years? Wow, just, just about five years or so.
Um, in this time, I, I, I have loved performing for you
here or on stage or in my bedroom, any anywhere, anywhere, really.
Um, I, I, yeah, wow.
Speaking, speaking of have a decade,
when I first joined Hololive, I had barely any experience in streaming or dancing or singing in front of people.
I couldn't even sing in front of my own mother.
Um, but
but now, now look at me, right? Um, I won't lie, it was really hard to get my footing.
Um, sometimes it was terrifying. No, a lot of the time, it was terrifying.
But spending time with you and all of the incredibly talented members of Hololive has been an absolute pleasure,
and I can truly say a highlight in my life. I will never forget my time here at Hololive.
I, I feel like I've been able to grow a lot in these past years,
not in height or brain activity, but
in my heart,
like my confidence,
my confidence in myself, I believe in myself a whole lot more now
than I did five years ago and...
Oh, it's thanks to you.
So, thank you everyone
for your compassion, your creativity, and your dedication to me.
Your Gumba.
Thank you to my Myth ladies.
We've been through so, so much together.
And I am honored to have been able to go on this journey with you girls.
Thank you to not-chan-mama for always working so hard and making me so darn cute.
And thank you to my Chum buds...
for always being there for me, for pushing me to try new games, new songs, new experiences.
Thank you for everything.
I've got a Gulf Stream current to catch.
Time to otsumete...
one last time.
Ready?
Otsu-same!
Take care, and be kind to yourselves, okay?
Okay.
Good night...
and goodbye.
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye.
Face to face with time again
We walk once more to the end
Burn it down, burn it down
Waves can't put out my flame
Death will never write my name
Burn it down, burn it down
They say the memory of me is fading
I've heard it all before
Don't tell me everyone around is waiting
And they all say
Tear it down, burn it down
And they'll all pay
When I tear it down, burn it down
When the world falls through
And all is ash again
While you all pretend
If this is the end, I'll do it again